(Raj:)Okay, how about you just
dip your toe in and meet one of them?
- Will you be there?
- Of course.
(Lucy:)Well, that's two. Three if you count me.
This is getting out of hand.
(Penny:)So then, during my afternoon shift,
I spilled an entire tray of drinks on myself.
- Oh, that's awful.
- Not really. My shirt was soaking wet.
(Penny:)I got, like, the biggest tip of my life.
(Leonard:)So listen, do you remember
when I said the similarities...
(Leonard:)...of the equations of general relativity
and hydrodynamics...
(Leonard:)...suggest you could find the equivalent
of Unruh radiation in a large body of water?
(Penny:)I thought I said that to you.
(Leonard:)Anyway, Stephen Hawking's team is looking
into that, and I've been invited to join them.
(Penny:)Wow, Hawking. Good for you.
(Leonard:)Well, it is,
just, you know, I'd be gone for a while.
- Well, how long?
- Three, four months.